A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Pupil Placement Board, 1957-1966
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Applications, 1959-1966., Extent: 224.35 cu. ft. (641 boxes). (Box 87-728)
  - Subseries II. Routine, 1957-1966., 217.7 cu. ft. (413 boxes) (Box 106-728)
    - Norfolk County (Motley - Ward), 1962-1964 (Box 329)
    - Norfolk County (Warner - Z) - Northampton County (A - O), 1962-1964 (Box 330)
    - Northampton County (P - Y) - Northumberland County (A - J), 1962-1964 (Box 331)
    - Northumberland County (K - Y) - Nottoway County (A - Hicks), 1962-1964 (Box 332)
    - Nottoway County (Hill - Z) - Orange County (A -C), 1962-1964 (Box 333)
    - Orange County (D - Z) - Page County (A - C), 1962-1964 (Box 334)
    - Page County (D - Z) - Patrick County (A - H), 1962-1964 (Box 335)
    - Patrick County (I - Y) - Pittsylvania County (A - H), 1962-1964 (Box 336)
    - Pittsylvania County (I - Y), 1962-1964 (Box 337)
    - Powhatan County - Prince George County (A - Doak), 1962-1964 (Box 338)
    - Prince George County (Dobson - L), 1962-1964 (Box 339)
    - Prince George County (M - Styer), 1962-1964 (Box 340)
    - Prince George County (Styles - Z) - Prince George County (Civil Rights Applications) - Prince William (A - Finnegan), 1962-1964 (Box 341)
    - Prince William (Fisher - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 342)
    - Princess Anne County (A - Gibbs), 1962-1964 (Box 343)
    - Princess Anne County (Giebler - O), 1962-1964 (Box 344)
    - Princess Anne County (P - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 345)
    - Pulaski County (A - Grantham), 1962-1964 (Box 346)
    - Pulaski County (Gravely - Nelson), 1962-1964 (Box 347)
    - Pulaski County (Nester - Weeks), 1962-1964 (Box 348)
    - Pulaski County (Wegner - Y) - Rappahannock County - Richmond County - Roanoke County (A - Armistead), 1962-1964 (Box 349)
    - Roanoke County (Arnold - Church), 1962-1964 (Box 350)
    - Roanoke County (Cisco - Fisher), 1962-1964 (Box 351)
    - Roanoke County (Fitzgerald - Hoke), 1962-1964 (Box 352)
    - Roanoke County (Holcomb - Manos), 1962-1964 (Box 353)
    - Roanoke County (Manspile - Pitts), 1962-1964 (Box 354)
    - Roanoke County (Plumb - Spindle), 1962-1964 (Box 355)
    - Roanoke County (Spitzer - Wilson), 1962-1964 (Box 356)
    - Roanoke County (Wimett - Z) - Rockbridge County (A - P), 1962-1964 (Box 357)
    - Rockbridge County (R - Z) - Rockingham County (A - Getz), 1962-1964 (Box 358)
    - Rockingham County (Gibson - Shipe), 1962-1964 (Box 359)
    - Rockingham County (Shipp - Z) - Russell County - Scott County (A -E), 1962-1964 (Box 360)
    - Scott County (F - W) - Shenandoah County (A - G), 1962-1964 (Box 361)
    - Shenandoah County (H - Troxell), 1962-1964 (Box 362)
    - Shenandoah (Truban - Z) - Smyth County (A - S), 1962-1964 (Box 363)
    - Smyth County (T - Y) - Southampton County - Spotsylvania County (A - L), 1962-1964 (Box 364)
    - Spotsylvania County (M - Z) - Stafford County - Surry County, 1962-1964 (Box 365)
    - Sussex County, 1962-1964 (Box 366)
    - Warren County - Washington County (A - C), 1962-1964 (Box 367)
    - Washington County (D - Y) - Westmoreland County (A - H), 1962-1964 (Box 368)
    - Westmoreland County (I - W) - Wise County (A - Large), 1962-1964 (Box 369)
    - Wise County (Laster - Z) - Wythe County (A - Dalton), 1962-1964 (Box 370)
    - Wythe County (Danner - Rodgers), 1962-1964 (Box 371)
    - Wythe County (Rogers - Z) - York County (A - Carty), 1962-1964 (Box 372)
    - York County (Caruthers - Hopkins), 1962-1964 (Box 373)
    - York County (Horner - Priem), 1962-1964 (Box 374)
    - York County (Prince - Williamson), 1962-1964 (Box 375)
    - York County (Willis - Z) - Alexandria (A - Bennett), 1962-1964 (Box 376)
    - Alexandria (Benson - Chock), 1962-1964 (Box 377)
    - Alexandria (Christensen - Dodson), 1962-1964 (Box 378)
    - Alexandria (Doescher - Gieck), 1962-1964 (Box 379)
    - Alexandria (Gikas - Henshaw), 1962-1964 (Box 380)
    - Alexandria (Hensley - Kimak), 1962-1964 (Box 381)
    - Alexandria (Kimmel - McBride), 1962-1964 (Box 382)
    - Alexandria (McCaddon - Nigro), 1962-1964 (Box 383)
    - Alexandria (Niland - Rapp), 1962-1964 (Box 384)
    - Alexandria (Rasberry - Sholtis), 1962-1964 (Box 385)
    - Alexandria (Shora - Teasdale), 1962-1964 (Box 386)
    - Alexandria (Tedlock - Williams), 1962-1964 (Box 387)
    - Alexandria (Williamson - Z) - Bristol (A - P), 1962-1964 (Box 288)
    - Bistol (Q - Y) - Buena Vista - Chesapeake (A - Battle), 1962-1964 (Box 389)
    - Chesapeake (Baugham - Corbin), 1962-1964 (Box 390)
    - Chesapeake (Corbitt - Gatling), 1962-1964 (Box 391)
    - Chesapeake (Gaudy - Johnson, E.), 1962-1964 (Box 392)
    - Chesapeake (Johnson, G. - Mills), 1962-1964 (Box 393)
    - Chesapeake (Miltier - Roberts), 1962-1964 (Box 394)
    - Chesapeake (Robertson - Totty), 1962-1964 (Box 395)
    - Chesapeake (Towe - Z) - Clifton Forge, 1962-1964 (Box 396)
    - Colonial Heights - Covington (A -Croy), 1962-1964 (Box 397)
    - Covington (Crush - Y) - Danville (A - Blevins), 1962-1964 (Box 398)
    - Danville (Boaze - Ellis), 1962-1964 (Box 399)
    - Danville (Ellison - Hunt), 1962-1964 (Box 400)
    - Danville (Hunter - Morris), 1962-1964 (Box 401)
    - Danville (Morrison - Slade), 1962-1964 (Box 402)
    - Danville (Slate - Z), 1962-1964 (Box 403)
    - Fredericksburg (A - Thomas), 1962-1964 (Box 404)
    - Fredericksburg (Thompson - Z) - Galax - Hampton (A - Banks), 1962-1964 (Box 405)
    - Hampton (Banning - Broad), 1962-1964 (Box 406)
    - Hampton (Brock - Chisman), 1962-1964 (Box 407)
    - Hampton (Chivolette - Day), 1962-1964 (Box 408)
    - Hampton (Dayhoff - Farrell), 1962-1964 (Box 409)
    - Hampton (Farris - Greer), 1962-1964 (Box 410)
    - Hampton (Greeson - Hodges), 1962-1964 (Box 411)
    - Hampton (hodsdon - Jorgensen), 1962-1964 (Box 412)
    - Hampton (Joseph - Linkous), 1962-1964 (Box 413)
    - Hampton (Linley - McNichol), 1962-1964 (Box 414)
    - Hampton (McNider - Norton), 1962-1964 (Box 415)
    - Hampton (Norvell - Privette), 1962-1964 (Box 416)
    - Hampton (Procissi - Shick), 1962-1964 (Box 417)
    - Hampton (Schilling - Squires), 1962-1964 (Box 418)
    - Hampton (Sreves - Turner), 1962-1964 (Box 419)
    - Hampton (Turney - Willson), 1962-1964 (Box 420)
    - Hampton (Wilson - Z) - Harrisonburg (A - K), 1962-1964 (Box 421)
    - Harrisonburg (L - Z) - Hopewell (A - E), 1962-1964 (Box 422)
    - Hopewell (F - Pope), 1962-1964 (Box 423)
    - Hopewell (Powell - Z) - Lynchburg (A - Blum), 1962-1964 (Box 424)
    - Lynchburg (Bobbitt - Daniel), 1962-1964 (Box 425)
    - Lynchburg (Daniels - Hamner), 1962-1964 (Box 426)
    - Lynchburg (Hampton - Long), 1962-1964 (Box 427)
    - Lynchburg (Longsworth - Pound), 1962-1964 (Box 428)
    - Lynchburg (Powell - Thomas), 1962-1964 (Box 429)
    - Lynchburg (Thompkins - Z) - Martinsville (A - Brooks), 1962-1964 (Box 430)
    - Martinsville (Brown - Minton), 1962-1964 (Box 431)
    - Martinsville (Mitchell - Y) - Norfolk City (A - Allcox), 1962-1964 (Box 432)
    - Norfolk City (Alle - Ayers), 1962-1964 (Box 433)
    - Norfolk City (Aydlett - Barry), 1962-1964 (Box 434)
    - Norfolk City (Berse - Berryman), 1962-1964 (Box 435)
    - Norfolk City (Berson - Bolt), 1962-1964 (Box 436)
    - Norfolk City (Bolton - Brake), 1962-1964 (Box 437)
    - Norfolk City (Bradley - Brown, F.), 1962-1964 (Box 438)
    - Norfolk City (Brown, G. - Burhans), 1962-1964 (Box 439)
    - Norfolk City (Burke - Carlson), 1962-1964 (Box 440)
    - Norfolk City (Carlton - Chavez), 1962-1964 (Box 441)
    - Norfolk City (Chavis - Cohen), 1962-1964 (Box 442)
    - Norfolk City (Cohn - Corpus), 1962-1964 (Box 443)
    - Norfolk City (Correll - Cunko), 1962-1964 (Box 444)
    - Norfolk City (Cunningham - Daye), 1962-1964 (Box 445)
    - Norfolk City (Daynude - Dorris), 1962-1964 (Box 446)
    - Norfolk City (Dorsett - Edge), 1962-1964 (Box 447)
    - Norfolk City (Edgerton - Ettline), 1962-1964 (Box 448)
    - Norfolk City (Ettner - Finn), 1962-1964 (Box 449)
    - Norfolk City (Finnegan - Frank), 1962-1964 (Box 450)
    - Norfolk City (Franklin - Gay), 1962-1964 (Box 451)
    - Norfolk City (Gayle - Gonder), 1962-1964 (Box 452)
    - Norfolk City (Gonsalus - Grey), 1962-1964 (Box 453)
    - Norfolk City (Gridley - Hall), 1962-1964 (Box 454)
    - Norfolk City (Hallengrn - Harris, M.), 1962-1964 (Box 455)
    - Norfolk City (Harris, N. - Helton), 1962-1964 (Box 456)
    - Norfolk City (Hemann - Holland), 1962-1964 (Box 457)
    - Norfolk City (Hollander - Hunt), 1962-1964 (Box 458)
    - Norfolk City (Hunter - Jewett), 1962-1964 (Box 459)
    - Norfolk City (Jiggetts - Jones, M.), 1962-1964 (Box 460)
    - Norfolk City (Jones, N. - Kight), 1962-1964 (Box 461)
    - Norfolk City (Kiker - Lamm), 1962-1964 (Box 462)
    - Norfolk City (Lammie - Lewis, J.), 1962-1964 (Box 463)
    - Norfolk City (Lewis, K. - Machak), 1962-1964 (Box 464)
    - Norfolk City (Machen - Matthews), 1962-1964 (Box 465)
    - Norfolk City (Mattingly - McLean), 1962-1964 (Box 466)
    - Norfolk City (McLearen - Miller, R.), 1962-1964 (Box 467)
    - Norfolk City (Miller, S. - Morris), 1962-1964 (Box 468)
    - Norfolk City (Morrisette - Nichols), 1962-1964 (Box 469)
    - Norfolk City (Nicholson - O), 1962-1964 (Box 470)
    - Norfolk City (P - Pendell), 1962-1964 (Box 471)
    - Norfolk City (Pender - Pope), 1962-1964 (Box 472)
    - Norfolk City (Popek - Redd), 1962-1964 (Box 473)
    - Norfolk City (Redden - Roberts, E.), 1962-1964 (Box 474)
    - Norfolk City (Roberts, F. - Rupp), 1962-1964 (Box 475)
    - Norfolk City (Rupport - Schwarz), 1962-1964 (Box 476)
    - Norfolk City (Schwebach - Siebert), 1962-1964 (Box 477)
    - Norfolk City (Siegel - Smith, M.), 1962-1964 (Box 478)
    - Norfolk City (Smith, N. - Squires), 1962-1964 (Box 479)
    - Norfolk City (Sroofe-Stultz), 1962-1964 (Box 480)
    - Norfolk City (Stump - Teal), 1962-1964 (Box 481)
    - Norfolk City (Teare - Traylor), 1962-1964 (Box 482)
    - Norfolk City (Traynor - Vetter), 1962-1964 (Box 483)
    - Norfolk City (Via - Watson, E.), 1962-1964 (Box 484)
    - Norfolk City (Watson,G. - Whited), 1962-1964 (Box 485)
    - Norfolk City (Whiteford - Williams, V.), 1962-1964 (Box 486)
    - Norfolk City (Williams, W. - Wright, E.), 1962-1964 (Box 487)
    - Norfolk City (Wright, F. - Z); Norton, 1962-1964 (Box 488)
    - Petersburg (A - Dawson), 1962-1964 (Box 489)
    - Peterburg (Dean - Jones, R.), 1962-1964 (Box 490)
    - Petersburg (Jones, S. - Robinson, E.), 1962-1964 (Box 491)
    - Petersburg (Robinson, F. - Williams), 1962-1964 (Box 492)
    - Petersburg (Williamson-Z) - Portsmouth (A-Blair), 1962-1964 (Box 493)
    - Portsmouth (Blake-Chambers), 1962-1964 (Box 494)
    - Portsmouth (Chambless-Dixon), 1962-1964 (Box 495)
    - Portsmouth (Dobbins-Giles), 1962-1964 (Box 496)
    - Portsmouth (Gillenwater-Horn), 1962-1964 (Box 497)
    - Portsmouth (Horne-Landon), 1962-1964 (Box 498)
    - Portsmouth (Landry-Mingo), 1962-1964 (Box 499)
    - Portsmouth (Minnick-Pope), 1962-1964 (Box 500)
    - Portsmouth (Popkey-Shy), 1962-1964 (Box 501)
    - Portsmouth (Sicard-Throne), 1962-1964 (Box 502)
    - Portsmouth (Thrower-Williams,S.), 1962-1964 (Box 503)
    - Portsmouth (Williams, T.-Z) - Radford, 1962-1964 (Box 504)
    - Richmond City (A - Bise), 1962-1964 (Box 505)
    - Richmond City (Bishko-Byrne), 1962-1964 (Box 506)
    - Richmond City (C-Corson), 1962-1964 (Box 507)
    - Richmond City (Cors-D), 1962-1964 (Box 508)
    - Richmond City (E-Goode), 1962-1964 (Box 509)
    - Richmond City (Goodle-Henry), 1962-1963; 1963-1964 (Box 510)
    - Richmond City (Henshaw-Johnson, G.), 1962-1964 (Box 511)
    - Richmond City (Johnson, H.-Lewis), 1962-1964 (Box 512)
    - Richmond City (Ley-Mickles), 1962-1964 (Box 513)
    - Richmond City (Middlebrook-Parker), 1962-1964 (Box 514)
    - Richmond City (Parkhurst-Riley), 1962-1964 (Box 515)
    - Richmond City (Rinehart-Sisk), 1962-1964 (Box 516)
    - Richmond City (Sisson-Terry), 1962-1964 (Box 517)
    - Richmond City (Texter-Wells), 1962-1964 (Box 518)
    - Richmond City (Welsh-Z) - Roanoke City (A), 1962-1964 (Box 519)
    - Roanoke City (B-D), 1962-1964 (Box 520)
    - Roanoke City (E-K), 1962-1964 (Box 521)
    - Roanoke City (L-R), 1962-1964. (Box 522)
    - Roanoke City (S-Z), 1962-1964. (Box 523)
    - South Norfolk - Staunton (A-C), 1962-1964. (Box 524)
    - Staunton (D-R), 1962-1964. (Box 525)
    - Staunton (S-Z) - Suffolk City, 1962-1964. (Box 526)
    - Virginia Beach - Waynesboro (A-Q), 1962-1964. (Box 527)
    - Waynesboro (R-Z) - Williamsburg, 1962-1964. (Box 528)
    - Winchester, 1964-1966. (Box 529)
    - Accomack (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 530)
    - Accomack (N-Z) - Albemarle (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 531)
    - Albemarle (N-Z) - Alleghany - Amelia - Appomattox (A-D), 1964-1966. (Box 532)
    - Appomattox (E-Y) - Amherst (A-O), 1964-1966. (Box 533)
    - Amherst (P-Y) - Augusta (A-Chittum), 1964-1966. (Box 534)
    - Augusta (Christian-G), 1964-1966. (Box 535)
    - Augusta (H-Mays), 1964-1966. (Box 536)
    - Augusta (McAlister-Simmons), 1964-1966. (Box 537)
    - Augusta (Simpkins-Z) - Bath, 1964-1966. (Box 538)
    - Bedford (A-D), 1964-1966. (Box 539)
    - Bedford (E-Martin), 1964-1966. (Box 540)
    - Bedford (Massey-S), 1964-1966. (Box 541)
    - Bedford (T-Z) - Bland - Botetourt (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 542)
    - Botetourt (G-Z) - Brunswick (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 543)
    - Brunswick (C-Short), 1964-1966. (Box 544)
    - Brunswick (Simmons-Y) - Buckingham - Campbell (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 545)
    - Campbell (C-Milton), 1964-1966. (Box 546)
    - Campbell (Minnix-Z); Caroline (A-H), 1964-1966. (Box 547)
    - Caroline (J-Y) - Carroll - Charles City - Charlotte (A-H), 1964-1966. (Box 548)
    - Charlotte (I-Y) - Chesterfield (A-Baskett), 1964-1966. (Box 549)
    - Chesterfield (Basl-Browder), 1964-1966. (Box 550)
    - Chesterfield (Brown-Clarke), 1964-1966. (Box 551)
    - Chesterfield (Clary-Davis, D.), 1964-1966. (Box 552)
    - Chesterfield (Davis, E.-Evans), 1964-1966. (Box 553)
    - Chesterfield (Eve-Gould), 1964-1966. (Box 554)
    - Chesterfield (Gouldman-Haught), 1964-1966. (Box 555)
    - Chesterfield (Haun-Jeffers), 1964-1966. (Box 556)
    - Chesterfield (Jefferson-Lamm), 1964-1966. (Box 557)
    - Chesterfield (Lamoreux-Lee), 1964-1966. (Box 558)
    - Chesterfield (Massie-Murphey), 1964-1966. (Box 559)
    - Chesterfield (Murphy-Philipp), 1964-1966. (Box 560)
    - Chesterfield (Phillips-Roberts), 1964-1966. (Box 561)
    - Chesterfield (Robertson-Showers), 1964-1966. (Box 562)
    - Chesterfield (Shredl-Syska), 1964-1966. (Box 563)
    - Chesterfield (T-Walker), 1964-1966. (Box 564)
    - Chesterfield (Wall-Wirt), 1964-1966. (Box 565)
    - Chesterfield (Wiewille-Z) - Clarke (A-Smallwood), 1964-1966. (Box 566)
    - Clarke (Smith-Z) - Culpeper - Cumberland, 1964-1966. (Box 567)
    - Dickenson, 1964-1966. (Box 568)
    - Dinwiddie - Essex(A-J), 1964-1966. (Box 569)
    - Essex(K-Y) - Fauquier (A-Foster), 1964-1966. (Box 570)
    - Fauquier (Foulks-Moore), 1964-1966. (Box 571)
    - Fauquier (Moran-White), 1964-1966. (Box 572)
    - Fauquier (Whitman-Z) - Floyd - Fluvanna - Franklin (A-Bowles), 1964-1966. (Box 573)
    - Franklin (Bowling-Jenkins), 1964-1966. (Box 574)
    - Franklin (Johnson-T), 1964-1966. (Box 575)
    - Franklin (U-Z) - Frederick (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 576)
    - Frederick (G-P), 1964-1966. (Box 577)
    - Frederick (R-Z) - Giles (A-Hale), 1964-1966. (Box 578)
    - Giles (Hall-Y) - Gloucester (A-J), 1964-1966. (Box 579)
    - Gloucester (K-Y) - Goochland (A-P), 1964-1966. (Box 580)
    - Goochland (Q-Y) - Grayson - Greene, 1964-1966. (Box 581)
    - Greenville - Halifax (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 582)
    - Halifax (C-Q), 1964-1966. (Box 583)
    - Halifax (R-Z) - Hanover (A-G), 1964-1966. (Box 584)
    - Henrico (A-Bishop), 1964-1966. (Box 585)
    - Henrico (Bivins-Campbell), 1964-1966. (Box 586)
    - Henrico (Campen-Crouch), 1964-1966. (Box 587)
    - Henrico (Crouse-E), 1964-1966. (Box 588)
    - Henrico (F-Grant), 1964-1966. (Box 589)
    - Henrico (Grantham-Hilkowitz), 1964-1966. (Box 590)
    - Henrico (Hill-Joyner), 1964-1966. (Box 591)
    - Henrico (Joynes-Lovings), 1964-1966. (Box 592)
    - Henrico (Lovvorn-Minter), 1964-1966. (Box 593)
    - Henrico (Mirril-Penick), 1964-1966. (Box 594)
    - Henrico (Penley-Root), 1964-1966. (Box 595)
    - Henrico (Roper-Snow), 1964-1966. (Box 596)
    - Henrico (Snyder-Turnbull), 1964-1966. (Box 597)
    - Henrico (Turner-Wilmore), 1964-1966. (Box 598)
    - Henrico (Wilson-Z) - Henry (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 599)
    - Henry (G-Sower), 1964-1966. (Box 600)
    - Henry (Spears-Z) - Highlands - Isle of Wight - King George - King and Queen (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 601)
    - King and Queen (N-Y) - King William - Lancaster, 1964-1966. (Box 602)
    - Lee, 1964-1966. (Box 603)
    - Loudoun (A-Harper), 1964-1966. (Box 604)
    - Loudoun (Harris-P), 1964-1966. (Box 605)
    - Loudoun (Q-Z) - Louisa (A-G), 1964-1966. (Box 606)
    - Louisa (H-Y) - Lunenburg (A-S), 1964-1966. (Box 607)
    - Lunenburg (T-Z) - Madison - Mathew (A-H), 1964-1966. (Box 608)
    - Mathews (I-W) - Mecklenburg (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 609)
    - Mecklenburg (G-N), 1964-1966. (Box 610)
    - Mecklenburg (O-Y), 1964-1966. (Box 611)
    - Middlesex - Montgomery (A-C), 1964-1966. (Box 612)
    - Montgomery (D-Maxwell), 1964-1966. (Box 613)
    - Montgomery (McBride-T), 1964-1966. (Box 614)
    - Montgomery (U-Y) - Nansemond (A-T), 1964-1966. (Box 615)
    - Nansemond (U-Z) - Nelson - New Kent - Northampton (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 616)
    - Northampton (G-Z) - Northumberland (A-C), 1964-1966. (Box 617)
    - Northumberland (D-Y) - Nottoway (A-I), 1964-1966. (Box 618)
    - Nottoway (J-Z) - Orange (A-G), 1964-1966. (Box 619)
    - Orange (H-Y) - Page (A-C), 1964-1966. (Box 620)
    - Page (D-Z) - Pittsylvania (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 621)
    - , 1964-1966. (Box 622)
    - Powhatan - Prince Edward (A-R), 1964-1966. (Box 623)
    - Prince Edward (S-W) - Prince George (A-Hawkins), 1964-1966. (Box 624)
    - Prince George (Hawks-Z), 1964-1966. (Box 625)
    - Pulaski (A-I), 1964-1966. (Box 626)
    - Pulaski (J-V), 1964-1966. (Box 627)
    - Pulaski (W-Y) - Rappahannock - Richmond County - Roanoke County (A), 1964-1966. (Box 628)
    - Roanoke County (B-Conner), 1964-1966. (Box 629)
    - Roanoke County (Cook-Glover), 1964-1966. (Box 630)
    - Roanoke County (Gloyd-J), 1964-1966. (Box 631)
    - Roanoke County (K-Morris), 1964-1966. (Box 632)
    - Roanoke County (Morrison-Sewell), 1964-1966. (Box 633)
    - Roanoke County (Sexton-Walker), 1964-1966. (Box 634)
    - Roanoke County (Wall-Z) - Rockbridge (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 635)
    - Rockbridge (G-K), 1964-1966. (Box 636)
    - Rockingham (L-Z) - Russell, 1964-1966. (Box 637)
    - Scott - Shenandoah (A-J), 1964-1966. (Box 638)
    - Shenadoah (K-W) - Smyth (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 639)
    - Smyth (N-Y) - Spotsylvania (A-P), 1964-1966. (Box 640)
    - Spotsylvania (Q-Z) - Stafford - Surry - Sussex (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 641)
    - Sussex (N-Z) - Tazewll (A-R), 1964-1966. (Box 642)
    - Tazewell (S-Z) - Warren - Washington, 1964-1966. (Box 643)
    - Westmoreland, 1964-1966. (Box 644)
    - Wythe (A-O), 1964-1966. (Box 645)
    - Wythe (P-Z) - York (A-D), 1964-1966. (Box 646)
    - York (E-T), 1964-1966. (Box 647)
    - York (U-Z) - Alexandria (A-Caper), 1964-1966. (Box 648)
    - Alexandria (Cason-Grade), 1964-1966. (Box 649)
    - Alexandria (Graham-Levick), 1964-1966. (Box 650)
    - Alexandria (Lewandowski-P), 1964-1966. (Box 651)
    - Alexandria (Q-Tread), 1964-1966. (Box 652)
    - Alexandria (Treese-Z) - Bristol - Buena Vista, 1964-1966. (Box 653)
    - Chesapeake (A-Dawson), 1964-1966. (Box 654)
    - Chesapeake (Day-James), 1964-1966. (Box 655)
    - Chesapeake (Jamison-Persell), 1964-1966. (Box 656)
    - Chesapeake (Person-Wesby), 1964-1966. (Box 657)
    - Chesapeake (West-Z) - Clifton Forge - Colonial Heights (A-P), 1964-1966. (Box 658)
    - Colonial Heights (Q-Y) - Danville (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 659)
    - Danville (C-Giles), 1964-1966. (Box 660)
    - Danville (Gill-King), 1964-1966. (Box 661)
    - Danville (Kingery-Phillips), 1964-1966. (Box 662)
    - Danville (Pickeral-Tinglof), 1964-1966. (Box 663)
    - Danville (Tipold-Z) - Fredericksburg (A-C), 1964-1966. (Box 664)
    - Fredericksburg (D-S), 1964-1966. (Box 665)
    - Fredericksburg (T-Z) - Galax - Hampton (A-Bowen), 1964-1966. (Box 666)
    - Hampton (Bowers-Davidson), 1964-1966. (Box 667)
    - Hampton (Davis-G), 1964-1966. (Box 668)
    - Hampton (H-Keels), 1964-1966. (Box 669)
    - Hampton (Keen-Milford), 1964-1966. (Box 670)
    - Hampton (Miller-Rhodes), 1964-1966. (Box 671)
    - Hampton (Rhone-Thomas), 1964-1966. (Box 672)
    - Hampton (Thomasson-Z), 1964-1966. (Box 673)
    - Harrisonburg - Hopewell (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 674)
    - Hopewell (C-Meeks), 1964-1966. (Box 675)
    - Hopewell(Melvin-Z) - Madison College (Harrisonburg), 1964-1966. (Box 676)
    - Martinsville (A-O), 1964-1966. (Box 677)
    - Martinsville (P-Z) - Norfolk City (A-Ballard), 1964-1966. (Box 678)
    - Norfolk City (Bellacer-Briley), 1964-1966. (Box 679)
    - Norfolk City (Bunso-Charles), 1964-1966. (Box 680)
    - Norfolk City (Charity-Davila), 1964-1966. (Box 681)
    - Norfolk City (Davis-E), 1964-1966. (Box 682)
    - Norfolk City (F-Grace), 1964-1966. (Box 683)
    - Norfolk City (Grady-Hennicks), 1964-1966. (Box 684)
    - Norfolk City (Henry-Johnson, L.), 1964-1966. (Box 685)
    - Norfolk City (Johnson, M.-Ledford), 1964-1966. (Box 686)
    - Norfolk City (Lee-McKay), 1964-1966. (Box 687)
    - Norfolk City (McKee-Myrick), 1964-1966. (Box 688)
    - Norfolk City (N-Phillips), 1964-1966. (Box 689)
    - Norfolk City (Philpot-R), 1964-1966. (Box 690)
    - Norfolk City (S-Smith, P.), 1964-1966. (Box 691)
    - Norfolk City (Smith, R.-Todd), 1964-1966. (Box 692)
    - Norfolk City (Tofalo-Whitson), 1964-1966. (Box 693)
    - Norfolk City (Whitt-Z) - Norton, 1964-1966. (Box 694)
    - Petersburg (A-C), 1964-1966. (Box 695)
    - Petersburg(D-I), 1964-1966. (Box 696)
    - Petersburg (J-P), 1964-1966. (Box 697)
    - Petersburg (Q-Wilkins), 1964-1966. (Box 698)
    - Petersburg (Wilkinson-Z) - Portsmouth (A-B), 1964-1966. (Box 699)
    - Portsmouth (C-G), 1964-1966. (Box 700)
    - Portsmouth (H-Mears), 1964-1966. (Box 701)
    - Portsmouth (Medlin-Sneed), 1964-1966. (Box 702)
    - Portsmouth (Snell-Z) - Radford (A-F), 1964-1966. (Box 703)
    - Radford (G-Y) - Richmond City (A-Aron), 1964-1966. (Box 704)
    - Richmond City (Aronberg-Blanton), 1964-1966. (Box 705)
    - Richmond City (Blathers-Brown), 1964-1966. (Box 706)
    - Richmond City (Browne-Cherry), 1964-1966. (Box 707)
    - Richmond City (Chestnut-Crews), 1964-1966. (Box 708)
    - Richmond City (Cridlin-Edmondson), 1964-1966. (Box 709)
    - Richmond City (Edward-Gass), 1964-1966. (Box 710)
    - Richmond City (Gaston-Harmon), 1964-1966. (Box 711)
    - Richmond City (Harper-Holler), 1964-1966. (Box 712)
    - Richmond City (Holley-Johnson, B.), 1964-1966. (Box 713)
    - Richmond City (Johnson, C.-Knight), 1964-1966. (Box 714)
    - Richmond City (Knighting-Manning), 1964-1966. (Box 715)
    - Richmond City (Manns-Millner), 1964-1966. (Box 716)
    - Richmond City (Mills-Overton), 1964-1966. (Box 717)
    - Ricmond City (Owen-Pruitt), 1964-1966. (Box 718)
    - Richmond City (Prussing-Rowe), 1964-1966. (Box 719)
    - Richmond City (Rowell-Smith, F.), 1964-1966. (Box 720)
    - Richmond City (Smith, G.-Taylor), 1964-1966. (Box 721)
    - Richmond City (Teachey-Waddy), 1964-1966. (Box 722)
    - Richmond City (Wade-Williams, B.), 1964-1966. (Box 723)
    - Richmond City (Williams, C-Z), 1964-1966. (Box 724)
    - South Boston - Staunton (A-I), 1964-1966. (Box 725)
    - Staunton (J-T), 1964-1966. (Box 726)
    - Staunton (U-Z) - Suffolk - Waynesboro (A-M), 1964-1966. (Box 727)